♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Coming this winter: actors
who don't look familiar
in shows you're pretty sure
you've never heard of
on networks you've
definitely never heard of.
First, it's The Marriage Man
on Geego Audience Prime Plus.
Then Frenemy on Goldstar.
And don't forget The
J. Tory Hampton Show on Traxx.
Lump Monkeys on Forge.
Comeuppance on LFR America.
Tattle Babies on Blitz Kids.
And Snapchatters on Perspire.
Who's watching them? Probably no one.
Are they comedies or dramas?
We're not even sure.
Turn your office watercooler
into a modern-day Tower of Babel.
- The Marriage Man!
- Lump Monkeys!
- The J. Tory Hampton Show!
Gay Paree!
TV: what a mess.
Hi, everybody.
You know how I've been dieting
like a maniac the last couple weeks?
Aw, damn it, that means
we're having people over.
We're having people over!
I just got off the phone with my mom,
and all the Pewterschmidts are
coming here for Thanksgiving.
I can't believe
you invited the whole family.
You know I hate big Thanksgivings.
Don't worry, Peter, it's gonna be fun.
And I can handle
most of the prep myself.
I just need you to go to the market
and get some extra napkins.
- That's not so bad.
- Oh. Pick up some wine for the adults.
I can do that.
A-And put the extra leaf
in the dining room table.
Oh, stop it. It's so simple.
Yeah, right. That table
ain't been opened in five years.
It'll be fine. Just don't drink
while you do it.
And for God's sake, don't lose
your temper with Chris.
All right, one, two, three.
Hup!
One more time.
Okay, all right, bend the knees.
Let's give it a good pull.
Hup!
Yeah, I think one side is stuck.
Do you, son? Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
Hup!
Hup! Hup!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
I think it's still stuck.
Oh, is that right?
Lot of narration.
It's like opening a table
with Ken Burns.
Um, why don't you go easy on that stuff?
This "stuff" is
the only thing stopping you
from getting
so karate-chopped right now.
Okay, big pull, on three.
All right, one, two, three.
Hup!
It's this one side, it's just stuck.
I know it's stuck!
Everyone sees it's stuck!
Are there voices you're hearing
shouting, "It's not stuck"?
'Cause if you hear any argument
from anybody who says it isn't stuck,
you send them to me, and I will
so karate-chop them in the face!
Got it?!
I'm not sure that that's...
What?! What aren't you sure about?
Hup!
Hup! Hup! Hup!
Hey, Chris. Table looks stuck.
Oh, really?
"Sky blue," says star witness.
You know what's crazy
about this time of year?
Everything is pumpkin spice.
We all follow your Twitter feed, Joe.
God, Thanksgiving
is such a pain in the ass.
I hate hosting.
I hear you, Peter.
I hate Thanksgiving, too.
Bonnie's sister is married
to a real show-off.
Denise, Wendell, it's great to see you.
- Wendell.
- Joseph.
It's just Joe. I think you know that.
My Thanksgiving's also a nightmare.
Donna's cousins are two-thirds
of Tony! Toni! Ton├й!
- Which ones?
- The "E" and the "I."
Aw, no Tony with a "Y."
That is correct.
We lack the alpha Tony.
Well, at least you guys
celebrate with your families.
Last year I spent Thanksgiving
with my old blow-up sex dolls.
Here you go, Carla.
See? We can do other things together.
How's the turkey? I made it myself.
Oh, don't look so surprised.
Ah. Someone's getting sleepy.
Must be the tryptophan.
I'll put a pot of coffee on.
Janet, coffee? Carla, coffee?
Dina, coffee? Sasha, coffee?
Dad, coffee?
I wish I had given you
more siblings, Glenn.
You know, sometimes I envy
the guys in the town jail.
They get a turkey dinner on Quahog
and don't have the hassle
of hosting their families.
Well, yeah, but they're in prison.
Nah, jail isn't prison.
Prison is big and scary.
Jail is just a sleeping deputy
with keys that can be grabbed
by a long broom handle
or a mischievous dog.
Do black people ever go to jail?
No. They go to prison.
Well, maybe going to jail
is what we should do.
- Peter, that's ridiculous.
- H-H-Hear me out, hear me out.
We'll commit a small crime
and get put in jail for a couple days.
- That's insane!
- Peter, Peter, you're crazy!
- Ridiculous!
- Lump Monkeys!
- Have you lost your mind?
All right, Joe,
there's chaos at the top.
Time to step up and be the leader
- of this group of friends.
- Lump Monkeys!
Guys, what if we all go to Vermont?
Let's just do Peter's thing.
Okay, if we want to get arrested,
the best way to do it is
to get caught on the Ring app
stealing people's packages.
I forgot to steal the package.
I think this is probably enough.
I don't know exactly what this is,
but this... this is crime.
Swanson!
Police Superintendent Chalmers.
My brother is superintendent
of the schools in Springfield.
Our parents divorced
when we were very young.
I was raised entirely by our mother,
he by our father.
We've never met.
There's a lot of backstory.
And you four are under arrest.
I can't believe the plan worked.
Here we are, the city jail.
What's going on? Why aren't we stopping?
You guys think you're the
first ones to have this idea?
The jail's already full of dads
getting out of Thanksgiving.
Well, if we're not going to Quahog jail,
where are we going?
The only place where
there's room for the weekend:
the state penitentiary.
You guys thinking what I'm thinking?
Wacky mug shot montage.
Hey, uh, are my friends coming?
No, they're all calling lawyers.
You used your one call on
this party photo booth guy.
Eh, we'll see who has
more fun this weekend.
Yeah, it just doesn't seem right.
We're in here,
and everyone on Wall Street
is free as a bird.
Joe, now is not the time for
your bland political musings.
This sucks. The courts are
closed for Thanksgiving,
which means we can't even
go before a judge till Monday.
That's five whole days here.
What the hell are we gonna do?
Well, if we're congress,
we'll do nothing.
All right, that one was sharp.
Good job, Joe.
And you know, maybe-maybe prison
won't be so bad.
Maybe we just got to
make the best of it.
Like those guys over there. Look.
They're playing leapfrog.
No one's jumping, though.
And that guy in the back
definitely has to get up higher.
Who taught these guys how to play?
Peter, please stop watching it.
Guys, I think we're in trouble here.
Come on, we're gonna be fine.
Joe, you should be
more terrified than any of us.
What if someone figures out
you're a cop?
It's not gonna happen.
I spent years undercover.
I'm a master of disguise.
What? You're in a wheelchair.
You can't disguise yourself as anything.
Is that so, Dad?
Chris? But that's impossible.
I've seen Chris standing up many times.
Have you?
Hey, Chris, I got two tickets
for the Sox.
- Want to go?
- You got it, Dad.
Oh, charley horse.
Oh, another charley horse, huh?
Well, you sit tight, Chris.
I can just take Joe's
brother-in-law Wendell.
Christopher.
It's just Chris. I think you know that.
The conjugal visit room is being used.
So, does your foot reach?
Peter, enough. You ruined Thanksgiving.
I have to host 20 people by myself.
- You smoke now?
- Yeah.
I have a husband in prison.
That's who smokes, genius.
Stewie, why do you look like
1976 Elton John?
I'm trying to keep a low profile.
You know that old sitcom premise
where the kid has two dates to the prom?
Well, I, um...
I may sorta, kinda be engaged
to four prisoners.
You're what? Stewie, that's crazy.
Oh, relax, Brian,
I'm just humoring them.
It's not serious.
Stewie, don't forget,
we're meeting DJs tomorrow.
Sure thing, Clint.
His mother thinks it's her wedding.
But we'll see.
How did you even meet these guys?
Easily. They were my pen pals.
You have prison pen pals?
Yes. A lot of people write prisoners.
Even Hollywood celebrity Kal Penn.
Kal Penn writes a prisoner?
Yeah. Ken. Lives in California.
You've never heard of
Kal Penn's pen pal Ken
in the Cal pen?
How could I possibly
have heard of Kal Penn's
pen pal Ken in the Cal pen?
Through this song.
♪ Well, I do get a yen
every now and then ♪
♪ To pick up a pen,
like my pal Kal Penn ♪
♪ And a note I will send
every now and again ♪
♪ To my pal Big Ben
who is locked in the pen ♪
♪ 'Cause he beat up some men
and he got five to ten ♪
♪ And he'll do it again ♪
♪ Dah, dah, dah-dah-dah ♪
♪ Kal Penn. ♪
- Who was that for?
- What are you talking about?
Phil Spector's in this prison.
Kid, I know talent and shooting
waitresses in the mouth,
and you've got talent.
We're gonna make a record.
God, every crevice
of this prison is terrifying.
Eh, it's not so bad.
I made one-eye contact with Bill Cosby.
Well, well, well.
Three "wells" is never a good sign.
- I think you guys have our lunches.
- Called it.
Uh, sorry, sir.
We don't want any trouble.
Yeah, we-we'll sit somewhere else.
Come on, guys,
let's avoid confrontation.
And whatever happens,
let's make sure
we're not goaded into fights
by simple playground taunts.
Damn. I was hoping for chicken.
Nobody calls me chicken.
Peter, no!
Aw, damn it, I lost a front tooth.
Well, hopefully in the prison yearbook
I'll just look
like a cute kindergartner.
Mad Dog, next time,
I'm asking
for the "top bunk".
LOL. Love Pete.
I'm starving.
We haven't eaten since we got here.
That's 'cause other prisoners
keep taking our meals.
And God knows what else
they're gonna do to us.
We have three more days here,
and we're not gonna survive
three more minutes.
That's 'cause you don't have a gang
- to protect you.
- A gang?
Yeah, when you're in a gang,
no one will mess with you.
That's why everyone joins one.
I used to be in a gang.
It was called the Republican party.
Our friend is very political.
So, how do we get
into one of these gangs?
Actually, you guys showed up
at the perfect time.
Tomorrow is the start
of Prison Rush Week.
Get in one, and you're home free.
That's a great idea!
Let's celebrate by pretentiously
analyzing some prison wine.
Okay, I'm getting notes of, um...
uh, well, feces.
Man, getting in a gang
is gonna be harder than I thought.
Speak for yourself, Peter.
What gang is this?
We're the Not Cops.
We're all definitely not cops.
So you think firemen are cool?
Firemen cook spaghetti.
And I think y'all know who I joined.
Are you now Kareem Abdul-Jableeveland?
I am Kareem Abdul-Jableeveland.
Hey, you know Muslims
can't drink alcohol, right?
I am Cleveland "Hurricane" Carter.
Well, Quagmire,
guess it's just you and me now.
Sorry, Peter, I'm in MS-13.
- What? How?
- It was easy.
- I said I was loco.
- Loco!
- Si.
- Muy loco.
Well, I can be loco.
I have a teardrop tattoo on my cheek.
Where? I don't see it.
Not-not that cheek.
Peter, that's
an unwiped watermelon seed.
- Loco?
- No. No loco.
Hey, Peter,
is that your baby over there?
We want fun. We want upbeat.
And for our dance,
we want "You Belong with Me"
by Taylor Swift.
Great, great. I also have
some more classic options,
- like "At Last."
- Okay.
So... so, what I need
is someone I can work with.
Can you be that person?
There you guys are.
I haven't seen you all day.
Me and the Not Cops
were watching Die Hard
and not commenting
on the believability of the police work.
Could John McClane
really foil a giant heist
outside his jurisdiction,
then just walk away
and do zero paperwork?
We don't know or care,
'cause we're not cops.
And I got my law degree.
I am now Cleveland J. Roman J. Israel,
and I will be wearing
wine-colored suits.
- You look crazy.
- Well, in his defense,
the movie was set in the '70s,
wasn't it?
No, it's modern-day.
Oh, my stars.
All right, everyone, that's lanch.
I mean, lunch. Sorry, it's my first day.
This sucks.
Everyone's eating lanch but me.
I'm never gonna find a gang.
Hey. You look like
you could use a friend.
Well, let's just say in prison,
this guy comes off.
I meant my gang.
We're looking for members.
- I-I bet you'd fit right in.
- Really?
You only have to do one thing first.
As the new white guy in prison,
you have to shiv the new black guy.
Oh, you guys are that kind of gang.
This is prison.
No one survives on their own.
So it's either him or you.
Man, I don't want to hurt Cleveland.
But I don't want to die.
And it would be nice
to have people to go
to Smash Mouth concerts with.
Wait, you guys go
to Smash Mouth concerts, right?
We're Nazis, Peter. We like Smash Mouth.
Come on, there's got to be a way
you'll let me in the gang
without shivving Cleveland.
Ooh, ooh, I got an idea.
There was this prison movie,
and-and there was this guy
who wanted to win over
the other prisoners,
and you know what he did?
He ate seven eggs. It was amazing.
So, you bring me seven
or some other reasonable amount
of eggs...
Peter, I know it's 50 eggs.
Ah, you're a film buff.
Yeah. Before this, I was
in the USC directors program.
Well, if you can call it that.
You think you're learning about film,
but, really, you're getting
a degree in politics.
I know,
everything is so political.
So political. Best advice I ever got:
whatever business you think you work in,
you really work in sales.
Because you're always selling yourself.
Yeah, wow, that is... that is good.
- You are smart.
- Well, I didn't say it.
- I'm just repeating it.
- Well, still,
y-you recognized its value.
That-That's not nothing.
Well, we're so happy you're all here.
We thought it might be fun
to kick things off
with a game of Heads Up!
- Daddy, do you want to start?
- No.
You just hold this up to your head,
and then we're gonna give you
clues to help you guess it.
I only like games with sticks.
Okay, ready?
Go.
Okay. It's a show.
Annie Get Your Gun.
No, it's on TV.
Oh. Poirot?
What is that? I've never heard of that.
Uh, it's a Belgian detective on PBS.
We just love it.
It's about seven castaways.
There's a professor
a-and a millionaire a-and a movie star.
- Poirot!
- No.
We already said it's not Poirot.
It's about people who took
a three-hour tour.
No, it's not.
It's about a Belgian detective.
It's on PBS.
The title character is played
by Bob Denver.
- It's pronounced "David Suchet."
- Who's that?
- I'm gonna guess Poirot.
- It's not Poirot!
Damn it, just pass!
Okay, this is a movie...
Roman J. Israel, Esq.
Yay!
Come on, Peter, it's him or you.
And-and he's not so great.
Don't forget, he's the one who told you
all those Schoolhouse Rock! Spoilers.
I had no idea
that bill would become a law.
Sorry, Peter.
My gang said I wasn't really loco
unless I shivved someone,
and you're the one guy
without gang protection, so...
Sorry, Quagmire.
As a Not Cop, I have to shiv
a guy in the Latin gang
and then blame it on Cleve...
No one made me do this.
I'm just sick of your overt racism.
Guys, guys, stop.
Stop. Look at us.
We're shivving each other
on Thanksgiving.
Oh, wait, no one shivved Cleveland.
But what are we doing?
What are all of us doing?
Fighting in here amongst ourselves
while Brooks is out there
waiting for all of us,
bagging groceries,
adapting to this new world seamlessly...
Brooks hung himself.
Oh, my stars.
The point is, in life,
you need to be thankful
for what you have.
I wasn't, and it got me in here.
I let down my family,
especially my wife.
I just wish she was here
so I could tell her I'm sorry.
I am here, Peter.
Not now, prison ladyboy
who talks like my wife
to please me sexually.
No, Peter, we're here.
Lois! What are you doing here?
I thought you were having
Thanksgiving with your parents.
Chris got caught
watching cousin Katie pee,
so that kind of ended things.
Well, I wanted to get caught. That's...
It's part of it.
And the truth is, Peter,
we're not a family without you.
Can you ever forgive me?
Of course I can, Peter.
- Hi, Peter.
- Who's your little friend?
Not now, Prison Lois.
So it's over?
And what was Venice?
Same thing it always was, babe:
a dream we both wanted to believe.
- Peter, who was that?
- Not now, Front-Sex Lois.
The important thing is,
my days of selfishness
and red-wig twinks are over.
I'm ready to come home with you.
But, Peter,
you're in here till next week.
Not anymore.
Hi, I'm the warden
and definitely not a psychotic prisoner
who just stabbed the warden
and stole his clothes.
Shh, shh!
Everyone, the warden's talking.
By the rules of prison
and The Love Boat,
you've made up,
which means you get to leave
wiser and happier.
I love you, Lois.
I love you, Peter.
Hey, Lois, one day, let's go to Venice.
- You promise?
- I said it, didn't I?
Donna!
- Bonnie!
- Sex doll!
Oh, yeah!
All right, guys, settle down.
Well, we're certainly glad
to have you home, Peter,
but I hope you learned your lesson.
I learned a hard lesson, Lois.
But it's not all bad.
I got to make a license plate
for our car
- that says "butthole."
- Isn't that too many letters?
Excellent question, Chris,
and yes, it is.
But I took off a "T"
and the "E" at the end.
I felt that was the right way to go.
Trust me, people will get it.
What's buthol?
- That's not how you say it.
- Yeah, I've heard of buthol.
It's some kind of alternative fuel.
You're ruining a smart joke.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome, for the first time,
Mr. and Mrs. Clint Beltran!
♪ At last... ♪
Hey!
You were right.
♪ My love ♪
♪ Has come along. ♪